singularlabs.com 2012-11-20

# Privacy Policy | SingularLabs

## Privacy

SingularLabs, its products and associated websites vehemently defends the privacy of all its users. We want everybody to feel safe using our site(s). This policy will clarify the use of any identifiable information gathered by this website.

### Use of Disclosed data:

SingularLabs will never share any personal information with third parties. Information that you have not personally disclosed but has been obtained through server logs (such as IP address, browser, operating system, screen resolution etc) will not be shared with users or other staff members. SingularLabs will never use this information with malicious intent such as hacking, spamming or spying.

### Contact Information

If you provide us with your email address (through our contact form or support forum), we will not send you spam or promotional material. Period. 

### Cookies:

Like many web sites, SingularLabs uses cookies to enhance your user experience (to remember your personal settings, for instance). Advertisements may display on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. 

### Advertising:

We use third-party advertising powered by Google to serve ads when you visit our website. Google may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Google, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Our primary advertising is provided by Google Adsense who utilize the doubleclick DART cookie to serve ads.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Analytics:

SingularLabs primarily utilizes the Google Analytics web service to monitor usage patterns and statistics of this website. As a result when you browse this website, some identifiable information will be shared with Google in order to aggregate statistics. We encourage you to read the Google privacy policy to familiarize yourself with how Google can use this information.

Server-side analytics containing non-identifiable information, such as IP address, country, browser, operating system and the resources you accessed while browsing our website are collected by SingularLabs. This information is not  accessible or distributed to the public, but rather is used to monitor usage patterns and look for errors, security exploits and activity of our server(s).

[CloudFlare Inc](http://cloudflare.com/) provides SingularLabs with usage statistics and analytics to assist in locating website bottlenecks and security issues. CloudFlare may monitor your browsing behaviour to protect its users from dangerous web traffic. 

### Desktop Applications Privacy:

SingularLabs frequently publishes programs for download freely on this and other websites. Our programs do not track any usage patterns or gather statistical information, and are completely free from Spyware. All outbound communication with the internet performed by our software will first require user permission or voluntary interaction.
